https://www.fnbalaska.com/bank-online/safe-and-secure/personal-online-banking-help

Toggle navigation
Industry Solutions
Industries
Industries
Medical & HealthcareTravel & TourismVeterinary ServicesResource DevelopmentAlaska Native EnterprisesTransportationConstruction
Meet Our Experts
Success Stories
Bernie's PharmacyAlaska Oral & Facial Cosmetic SurgeryGreen Earth LandworksThe Native Village of UnalakleetMeeting Your NeedsThompson & Co PRHu Family DentistryCool Cache FarmsAlaska Rubber & RiggingCapstone Family MedicineCommercial Kitchen Solutions
Major Marine Tours: Making Dreams Come True
»
Business Banking
Manage Your Money
Checking AccountsSavings AccountsMoney Market DepositsSafe Deposit ServicesCash ManagementBusinessManagerConvenience BankingOnline & Mobile Banking
Meet Our Experts
Fuel Your Business
Business DebitBusiness and Corporate Mastercard Credit CardsMerchant ServicesLoans for StabilityLoans for GrowthEscrow ServicingWealth ManagementBusiness NewsletterDownloadable Forms
Skinny Raven Sports: Customer since 1994
»
Personal Banking
Manage Your Money
Checking AccountsSavings AccountsMoney Market DepositsSafe Deposit ServicesCDs and IRAsConvenience BankingOnline & Mobile Banking
Apply for a Loan
Achieve Your Goals
Personal Debit Mastercard CardsPersonal Mastercard Credit CardsPersonal LoansHome Equity LoansEscrow ServicingWealth ManagementDownloadable Forms
Bank on the Go: Deposit Checks & Pay Bills
»
Home Loans
Find the Right Loan
Home Loan ProgramsClosing Cost AssistanceHome Construction Loans
Prequalify & Apply
Tools
Meet Our TeamBorrower Application PortalHelpful CalculatorsFAQs
Dr. Gay: Moving a Family, Building a Practice
»
Careers
Current Positions
Why Work at First National?Equal Opportunity EmployerManagement Associate Program
Search New Careers
Current Employees
Looking for opportunities to advance? Log in to access your employee account and get started.
Employees Click to Log In
Learn about Career Opportunities at First National
»
Bank Online
Account Login
Account:
Personal
Business
Business Manager
Wealth Management
Personal Credit Card
Business Credit Card
SmartData Gen 2
Easy A/P
Your Username:
Your Password:
Forgot Password? Click here.
1st Time Login —
Business ·
Personal
Online Help —
Business ·
Personal
Unauthorized use is a crime punishable by federal laws. Protect your personal data.
Security Info.
Safe and Secure
Business Online Banking SupportPersonal Online Banking SupportMastercard RegistrationElectronic StatementsSecurity Info & Fraud Alerts
Banking Education: For Home & Business
»
About Us
About First National
Our CommitmentOur MissionBoard of DirectorsLeadership TeamYour Banking TeamAlaska's EconomyCommunity SupportPress ReleasesFinancial ReportsReport Misconduct
Helpful Shortcuts
Branches & ATMsCurrent RatesProperty SalesAlaska's EconomyWebsite Search
In the Community: New Year's Day Giving
»
FNBee
Personal Online Banking SupportFrequently Asked Questions
How do I log in for the first time?
If you already have your first time login code:
Click here to proceed to the first time login screens.
Take a look at the Personal Online Banking Guide (3 MB PDF).
If you don't have a first time login code:
Call 777-4FNB (4362) in Anchorage/Eagle River OR 1-800-856-4FNB (4362) in other communities. Have your personal savings or checking, loan, or certificate of deposit account information handy. Tell our friendly Customer Service Representative you want to use Online Banking for the first time. You'll soon have everything you need to get started.
If you're already using First National's Telephone Banking:
You can use your six-digit numerical password to login to online banking for the first time.
If you're not a First National customer:
Talk to the friendly Alaskans at the Customer Service phone numbers above. Find out how easy it is to put the financial power and experience of First National to work for you.
How do I access my trust account online?
For online trust account access, you'll first need to go through an online account request process. You'll be required to provide the SSN and email address that was given to your administrator when your account was set up.
Protect your personal information. Use a secure WiFi connection when logging into Online Banking.
Watch Video Tutorials
Bank Now! Online
Enhanced Online Security
Bill Pay
Mobile Deposit
Zelle®
Identity Theft Prevention
See All Videos »
Online & Mobile Banking
e-Services from First National Bank Alaska aren't just about convenience—they're better all around! Your financial privacy is more secure with online banking. You're more efficient, with online bill-pay. And you're greener, when you opt to receive electronic statements instead of printed ones.
Protect your personal information by using a secure Wi-Fi connection when logging into Online Banking or transmitting any non-public information. If a Wi-Fi network does not require a password, it may not be secure.
Access Your Account From Anywhere
Real-time access to your personal account information from anywhere in the world, 7 days a week, 24 hours a day. If you're a bank customer, when using Online Banking you can:
Check your account balances
View new and old transactions
Transfer funds between accounts
Make payments to your First National Bank Alaska escrow, Mastercard® account, or loan
View, download and/or print images of your cleared checks
View, download and/or print your monthly electronic statement
And when you use Online Banking, you can also export account data to Quicken™ (.qis), comma separated file (.csv) and open financial exchange (.ofx) formats.
Available for Tablets and Smartphones
Manage your personal finances anytime, anywhere on your tablet device or smartphone while enjoying the security you’ve come to expect from First National.
How it Works
Check account balance and recent transactions
Transfer funds between your accounts
Make online bill payments
Follow turn-by-turn directions to the nearest branch
View check images and deposit slips
Review PENDING transaction status
Access the minimum amount due and due date for loans
Log in to the FNBApp with Touch ID (iPhone 5s or later model)
And set other features — learn more
Download the FNBApp for Mobile Devices
Apple Store
Google Play
To set up Online Banking for the first time or to set up Online Banking using the FNBApp, contact Customer Service at 777-4362 or 1-800-856-4362 to obtain a first time log in code.
Message and data fees may apply.
Protect your personal information. Use a secure WiFi connection when logging into Online Banking.
“Efficiency Is The Cat's Meow In Flat Economy”
You are about to leaveFirst National Bank Alaska’s web site.
First National Bank has no control over and claims no responsibility for the content, products,
services or recommendations provided by or advertised on linked sites.
First National Bank does not endorse, make any warranty either express or implied, or guarantee content,
products, services or recommendations provided by or advertised on linked sites. Linked sites may have
a privacy policy different from First National Bank and may provide less security.
Are you sure you wish to continue?
YES NO
You are using an outdated and
potentially insecure browser.
This website is designed to work with all modern browsers and relatively recent versions.
Due to the age of your browser, certain aspects of the site may behave incorrectly or in unexpected ways.
In addition, your browser may not support the most current encryption protocols which are required by our online banking systems,
and which are in place for your safety.
While you may proceed to the website, we strongly advise you to upgrade. We recommend the current version of Chrome (click here to download).
Are you sure you wish to continue?
YES NO
